DIANA PINON

• DETAILS •

+1 (309) 339 4876 dianapinonb@gmail.com

o LINKS o

LinkedIn

Github

Personal Portfolio

o SKILLS o

Ruby on Rails

JavaScript

CSS

HTML5

Bootstrap

Relational Databases

GitHub

PostgreSQL

Analytical and Problem-Solving

High Attention to Detail

Fast Learner

Adaptability

Leadership

Ability to Work in a Team

Microsoft Excel

Microsoft Office

SAP

Supply Chain Guru

• LANGUAGES •

Spanish

English

French

PROFILE

Versatile industrial and supply chain engineer with 6+ years of experience. Having discovered a passion for coding, I finished a full-stack web development bootcamp and am now looking for new challenges as a developer or a supply chain professional.

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Developer, Le Wagon, Mexico City

October 2020 — December 2020

Product manager for Booklub

MSc. Supply Chain and Lean Management, Toulouse Business School, Toulouse

September 2016 — March 2018

Double degree with École des Mines d'Albi. Awarded Summa Cum Laude.

Bachelor's Degree in Industrial Engineering, Instituto Tecnológico de Chihuahua, Chihuahua

August 2008 — March 2013

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Sr. Management Consultant at CGN Global, Chicago

April 2018 — Present

Enabled the growth strategy of a \$17B USD coffee roasting and a food processing company through the evaluation and redesign of their supply chain.

Process Engineer at Safran Electrical & Power, Chihuahua

July 2014 — July 2016

Increased manufacturing cell's efficiency from 53% to 96% in a five-month period, while reducing internal quality issues and having no quality escapes to the customer.

Invoiced Not Delivered (IND) Auditor at Cadena Comercial OXXO, Chihuahua

January 2013 — July 2014

Generated ~\$40k USD savings by reducing IND from 0.23% to 0.12% in 18 months.

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATIONS

Network Optimization, Chicago

June 2021

Certified Demand-Driven Planner, Toulouse

December 2017

Yellow Belt in Lean Management, Toulouse

March 2017

Certified Associate in Project Management, Toulouse

February 2017

Basics of Supply Chain Management, Toulouse

December 2016